var questions =[{
"question": "The theremin belongs to this class of musical instruments:",
"option1": "a) Keyboard",
"option2": "b) Electronic",
"option3": "c) Wind",
"option4": "d) Percussion",
"answer": "2"
}, {                        //one object with 6 propoties
"question": "Which of these is not a type of African Drum?",
"option1": "a) Gudugudu",
"option2": "b) Talking Drum",
"option3": "c) Djembe",
"option4": "d) Timpani",
"answer": "4"
}, {
"question": "How many pedals does a grand piano have?",
"option1": "a) 3",
"option2": "b) 1",
"option3": "c) 2",
"option4": "d) 4",
"answer": "1"
}, {
"question": "The saxophone is a popular jazz instrument, but what was it's first use?",
"option1": "a) Military music",
"option2": "b) Wall ornament",
"option3": "c) drowing out flutes",
"option4": "d) Bluegrass music",
"answer": "1"
}, {
"question": "What is the name for the end of a horn that projects sound?",
"option1": "a) Gong",
"option2": "b) Euphonium",
"option3": "c) Barrel",
"option4": "d) Bell",
"answer": "4"
}, {
"question": "What is the word for a kind of stringed instrument?",
"option1": "a) Harmonica",
"option2": "b) Harpy",
"option3": "c) Harp",
"option4": "d) Trombone",
"answer": "3"
}, {
"question": "How many strings does a cello have?",
"option1": "a) 3",
"option2": "b) 2",
"option3": "c) 4",
"option4": "d) 1",
"answer": "3"
}, {
"question": "Which of these instruments require a reed in order to be played?",
"option1": "a) Clarinet",
"option2": "b) Lute",
"option3": "c) Flute",
"option4": "d) Viola",
"answer": "1"
}, {
"question": "What is the literal translation of ukulele, a traditional Hawaiian instrumment?",
"option1": "a) Little guitar",
"option2": "b) Jumping flea",
"option3": "c) Dull ax",
"option4": "d) Fly swatter",
"answer": "1"
}, {
"question": "Which one of these is not a percussion instrument?",
"option1": "a) Tom-tom",
"option2": "b) Crash cymbal",
"option3": "c) Snare drum",
"option4": "d) Flute",
"answer": "4"
}];   //10 objects in array